shopatmajorbrands.com 2012-03-24

# About Us - Online Shopping in Delhi |Bangalore | Hyderabad | Mumbai

What Information Do We Collect?

We collect information from you when you register on Shopatmajorbrands.com site or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

What Do We Use Your Information?

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offering based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service request and support needs).
  * To process transactions.

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased products or service requested by the customer. we do not collect or receive your credit card information.

  * To send periodic emails

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related products or services information, etc.

Note: if at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.  
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

How Do We Protect Your Information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information, accounts and financial details.

  * Do we use cookies?

We do not use cookies.

  * Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies or protect ours or others rights properly or safety.

  * Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

Governing Law and Jurisdiction

This User Agreement shall be construed in accordance with the applicable laws of India. The Courts at Mumbai shall have exclusive jurisdiction in any proceedings arising out of this agreement.

Any dispute or difference either in interpretation or otherwise, of any terms of this User Agreement between the parties hereto, the same shall be referred to an independent arbitrator who will be appointed by Major Brands India Private Limited. and his decision shall be final and binding on the parties hereto. The above arbitration shall be in accordance with the Arbitration and Conciliation Act, 1996 as amended from time to time. The arbitration shall be held in Mumbai. The High Court of judicature at Mumbai alone shall have the jurisdiction and the Laws of India shall apply.

Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page and such changes will be effected at our discretion.

Modification of Terms and conditions of Service

shopatmajorbrands.com may at any time modify the User Agreement without any prior notification to you. Management decision of the shopatmajorbrands.com would be the final decision Subsequent to any modification of the User Agreement; we will inform you of the modifications in the User Agreement via e-mail at the address provided by you while registering on shopatmajorbrands.com. You can access the latest version of the User Agreement at any given time on shopatmajorbrands.com. You should regularly review the User Agreement on shopatmajorbrands.com. In the event the modified User Agreement is not acceptable to you, you should discontinue using the service. However, if you continue to use the service you shall be deemed to have agreed to accept and abide by the modified User Agreement.
